Keep runnin' along.
Watch as we pass by.
As we raise our flag.
Up high in the sky.
Alright, here we go now.
Sailing through the endless ocean.
Facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure.
Nobody has ever.
Got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep
believing in our dreams.
And let our heart lead the way.
Then once we got all that.
All there's left is to go.
When we face the dark and stormy weather.
Keep the pace.
We'll link our hearts together.
Then I'm sure we'll make it through.
No matter what.
Keep running along, keep running along.
Still raising our flag as we journey on.
Though our chances are close to none.
We won't back down from anyone.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
Toward our own dreams
while keeping the pace.
With a compass pointing to our goal.
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world.
Start me up.
Keep running along, keep running along.
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top.
There's no way that we'll ever quit.
We'll keep heading for tomorrow.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
I see through your eyes,
what we'll have to face.
All the memories will stay in our hearts.
We'll never let them go, brand new world.
Start me up.
Is on the line but I'm warning you
I won't make the same mistake twice.
I don't care if you're a woman if you don't
give me that key you're gonna get hurt.
We've gone from sweet
talk to petty threats.
Have we do you think I care if
you treat me like a woman or not.
I'm an assassin a professional.
Keep your chivalry.
I've been ordered to take your life
and that's exactly what I'll do.
Take my life huh?
Afraid that's not gonna
work because I'm not
leaving here without the
key to those handcuffs.
I suppose tea time is over.
Then you CP9
folks are every
bit as strong as you say.
Gotcha!
Score one point for me.
You!
How could you?
Sorry, but that's how you score a point.
Uh, you're gonna pay for that one?
He's fast.
There, it's over.
You're pinned to the ground.
I beat you fair and square.
Now give me the key.
Free your pistol.
Temper!
What a sad little man.
You call yourself a pirate?
You're afraid to even touch me.
Hey, you shut up!
Give me the damn key!
I've had enough of your
empty threats, you coward.
I'm growing bored, so
let's try something new.
If you can't withstand this
attack, you won't survive.
He's not coming after me.
I was lucky enough to get away once.
I'd be dead for sure next time!
I need to find the others.
Before he finds me?
Life return.
Damn!
Let's see.
What comes next?
Shall I pierce thee to death?
Or choke thee to death.
A fragile life.
A wintry wind.
Now, before spring can come.
A flower succumbs to the cold.
But in its end.
Let it bloom in red.
If only for an instant.
This is my compassion.
as the petals gently fall.
Yaw!
A final request.
When you reach the other side,
I ask that you deliver a message
to my poor deceased mother.
Let her know that I am well and that my
killer's instinct is as strong as ever.
Now die.
Die.
Die! Die!
No!
Song of Springfield!
Movin' rules!
Nambi, are you OK?
I'm fine.
Thank you for saving me.
Did he eat a Devil Fruit?
What's up with his hair?
I don't know.
It's like he's got an octopus on his head.
Once he grabs you, you're done for.
Come on, this is our chance to get away.
The less we see of that guy, the better.
Hey, wait.
But how are we supposed to get the key?
Oh, this little thing.
Stealing the key was the easy part.
I just couldn't deal
with that hair of his.
Anyway, have you seen the others before?
I get to that.
Could you tell me what number your key is?
It has a number.
Oh, it's three.
Wrong one.
You're gonna have to explain this to me.
This place is falling apart.
Wait, what?
Is that a doll?
No
It's Sanji
What the heck happened to him?
Sanji, can you hear me?
What's going on?
Who did this to you?
Are you alright?
Say something
Sanji!
I'm sorry.
I lost.
I couldn't get the key. Hold on, okay.
I'll see what I can do.
Sanji lost?
I can't believe it.
Hey, Sanji.
You really couldn't win?
You really gave it your all?
You fought that blonde
woman, didn't you? I see.
You must have gone easy on her.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't get the key.
Forget the key!
This fight is a matter of life and death.
You can't stick to your
stupid code of honor, okay?
Is chivalry really worth dying for?
People are counting on you!
I don't want this.
I don't want to die.
But I was raised to never
hit a lady, no matter what,
so even at a time like this,
even if it kills me, I won't kick a woman.
I see.
That's stupid.
He was coughing up blood!
Nami, don't hit him!
Is running away against
your coat of honor, too?
Because that's not worth
dying over, either.
Nobody wants to see you
throw your life away in vain.
Leave that woman to me.
You try to get better.
By the way, even if it's dumb, I
like that chivalry of yours. What?
Did she say she loved me?
Not even close.
For the record, I won't play nice.
Neither will I.
We'll get along fine.
Yoyoy!
I have returned at last!
Not him again.
Stop right there!
I won't let you escape
from me, understand?
Don't deal with that woman up there, Nami!
Leave this guy to me!
Right, got it!
Yo-yo-yo-yo-yo!
Just try and stop me! Cloven!
Wow!
Are you okay, pirate guy?
Guys, you're not looking so good!
Push it out.
Jeez, there's no way that little boat
was going to make it across there.
Are you stupid or something?
You don't understand.
Robin's being taken through those gates.
I have to hurry or I won't
be able to bring her back.
What do you think you're doing?
Hold on, Mr. Pirate! Calm down!
We came to tell you that we found a way
to get over to the Gates of Justice!
Here the awesome is for
showing me this tunnel!
How'd you know about it, anyway?
We caught Lucci going down the stairs
with that noisy servant of his!
That guy was talking and laughing so much,
they didn't notice that
we were behind them!
There's no way those pirates will
figure out where the entrance is!
They'll never find us!
Lucci and that black-haired pirate lady
went through the secret doorway, too!
Hmm.
So this is it, huh?
Man, this door is pretty thick.
Do you know how to open it?
Well, Luchi's servant was messing
around with something over here.
I bet you unlock it
using this big keyhole.
But I don't see a key.
All right, stand back. Why?
What are you going to do?
Yeah, this is the way we
need to go to get there right
It's open!
Alright, time to head out!
No way!
Hatchi, make yourself all tiny!
you sure are funny mr.
pirate guy wait did you
just hear a loud noise
or did i imagine it No
it couldn't be it was
nothing maybe it was the
sound of one of the pirates
breaking down The door
what impossible don't be
absurd first off those
are thick iron doors we're
talking about And secondly
there's no way they
could have even found
them in the first place it
was nothing Actually there
is a way a child and her
pet were following us
they could have Told them
but if you saw them why
didn't you stop them
because I wasn't ordered
To do so what you gotta
be kidding me you should
be able to make that call
About something so obviously
wrong you idiot don't
you realize what could
Happen so you're telling
me that those damn Pirates
are most likely on their
way down here right now
all right back to normal
Hang on robin
Stupid pigeon guy i can't
wait to kick your ass damn i'm
slowing down gotta refill my
cola as as soon as possible.
He moves around pretty fast for a big guy.
Jumps high too.
Cha-ba-ba, looking for me?
Damn straight, but you keep running away.
Cha-ba-ba,
well, if you were a little faster, maybe
I'd actually feel one of those punches?
you're so proud of.
Franky Triangle Jacker!
Cha-ba-ba, think your
sideburns can hurt me?
Not a chance!
Gotcha!
Weapons left!
Damn, that was just about
the last of the cola.
Gotta get to that kitchen quick!
Ha!
Not so fast!
Bastard, you dodged my attack!
What, you afraid it
might actually hurt ya?
Chaba!
What's that?
What's wrong, coward?
Shouldn't you run off by now? Coward?
No one calls me that!
You just pissed off the wrong guy!
How'd you like a taste of my killer fists?
Here's my own special punch
combined with a finger pistol!
Solid beast!
Chaba-ba!
Whoa, pathetic.
That's got nothing on.
My strong... Iron body!
Huh?
Is that all you got?
That was the weakest punch ever.
All your punches are lazy and flat.
No way your punches are
the lazy and flabby ones!
They're like flimsy
underpowered paper punches.
Yours are flimsy underpants punches.
Underpowered, not underpants!
You're underpowered pants!
Oh, yeah?
Well, you're a stupid bra!
Shut up, pair of socks! Long jaws!
Boxer briefs!
White cloths!
Get off me!
Shut your chains, purse hole!
Oh, all right.
Finally made it into the kitchen.
Whoa, jackpot.
Look at the size of that fridge.
Hey, he changed.
Gorilla Devil Fruit
Powers, maybe? Damn it.
My three minutes are already up.
I used the rumble ball
too early in the fight.
What now?
Yo-yo!
You will now disappear from this world.
Finishing bro!
First time!
Yes, it has a lock!
Champa! Kumadori!
All right!
I locked him up! Why, you...
Hey, hold on a second.
I got some business with
that fridge, Gorilla Man.
Ah!
CP9 and that jerk! It's Franky!
I'm on your side, remember?
Who are you calling Gorilla Man?
Damn, you're slow!
Listen up.
I'm just like Luffy.
I haven't forgiven you
for what you did to us.
We lost a member of our crew.
And it's all your fault, you bastard!
Give us our own salt back!
What are you talking about?
You were just with him!
Look, forget about all that for now.
Do you want to get Nico Robin back or not?
I do! Robin!
Then turn around, get three bottles of cola
out of that fridge and give them to me.
That'll bring me back up to full power.
After that,
I'll be able to pound these jerks into
the ground and take their keys no problem.
What kind of an idiot
gets stronger from cola?
I do! Don't judge me!
How long do you two plan on
keeping up this comedy act?
You want to stop for a little tea
party in the middle of a fight?
That's not only stupid, it's rude!
Secret technique?
No! Now thrashing! No!
Shababababababa!
Beats left!
You call that an attack?
This is terrible! He's right!
He's fighting on our side now!
I bet he's right!
I better help him!
Shabba ba ba ba ba!
If I open and close the door
really fast, then he can't escape!
Now! Yo-yo!
The door has suddenly opened!
Yes!
Franky!
Catch!
You're a lifesaver!
Oh, feelin' fresh!
Oh!
Uh, what the?
Fresh is the best!
Vegetable punch, go!
Solid beast.
That was vegetable juice, jerk!
How am I supposed to
power up on that crap?
Cola, damn it! Cola!
I just thought he was really thirsty.
Yo-yo-yay!
The door!
Coming out, Jack! Thanks, man!
My heart is failing!
And now...
I'll sit a spell.
I've tended to the fields
enough for one day, neighbor.
Let's stop all this fighting.
Kick our feet up, have
ourselves a nice cup of tea.
Tea does a body good.
That's not cola either, dumbass!
He is the funniest thing ever.
Hey!
Stop looking at me with that.
I wonder what else might happen when I
give him other drinks, Vice little bastard.
Get it right, Antlerhead!
So, the change doesn't depend
on what mood you're in?
Cola only now!
There it is.
The real stuff.
That's cola for sure.
Come to papa.
I don't know what's going on, but there's
no way I'm letting you get what you want.
Drop this key!
No, Franky!
Super!
Oh, come on.
It's not like anything's gonna
change because you drank some cola.
Get ready.
Chop, for what?
Another round of your flimsy punches?
Give me a break.
Strong...
Hammer!
Go, baby!
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Amazing!
Oh, you were right.
My punches were pretty flimsy.
But don't worry, that's all gonna change.